[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Question 1: Which of the below are reserved keyword in Java?",
      "option": [
        {"optionid": 1, "name": "array"},
        {"optionid": 2, "name": "goto"},
        {"optionid": 3, "name": "null"},
        {"optionid": 4, "name": "int"}
      ],
      "answer": 2,
      "selected": 0
    }
    ,
       {
         "id": 2,
         "question": "Question 2: Which of the below are unchecked exceptions in java??",
         "option": [
           {"optionid": 1, "name": "RuntimeException"},
           {"optionid": 2, "name": "ClassCastException"},
           {"optionid": 3, "name": "NullPointerException"},
           {"optionid": 4, "name": "IOException"}
         ],
         "answer": 1,
         "selected": 0
       },
       {
         "id": 3,
         "question": "Question 3: Which is a valid keyword in java?",
         "option": [
           {"optionid": 1, "name": "interface"},
           {"optionid": 2, "name": "string"},
           {"optionid": 3, "name": "Float"},
           {"optionid": 4, "name": "unsigned"}
         ],
         "answer": 1,
         "selected": 0
       },
       {
         "id": 4,
         "question": "Question 4: Which is the valid declarations within an interface definition?",
         "option": [
           {"optionid": 1, "name": "public double methoda();"},
           {"optionid": 2, "name": "public final double methoda();"},
           {"optionid": 3, "name": "static void methoda(double d1);"},
           {"optionid": 4, "name": "protected void methoda(double d1);"}
         ],
         "answer": 1,
         "selected": 0
       },
       {
         "id": 5,
         "question": "Question 5: Which one is a valid declaration of a boolean?",
         "option": [
           {"optionid": 1, "name": "boolean b1 = 0;"},
           {"optionid": 2, "name": "boolean b3 = false;"},
           {"optionid": 3, "name": "boolean b5 = no;"},
           {"optionid": 4, "name": "boolean b1 = 1;"}
         ],
         "answer": 2,
         "selected": 0
       },
       {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Question 6: Which is a valid declarations of a String?",
        "option": [
          {"optionid": 1, "name": "String s1 = null;"},
          {"optionid": 2, "name": "String s3 = (String) abc;"},
          {"optionid": 3, "name": "String s2 = 'null';"},
          {"optionid": 4, "name": "String s4 = (String) '\ufeed';"}
        ],
        "answer": 1,
        "selected": 0
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Question 7: What is the name of the method used to start a thread execution?",
        "option": [
          {"optionid": 1, "name": "init();"},
          {"optionid": 2, "name": "start();"},
          {"optionid": 3, "name": "run();"},
          {"optionid": 4, "name": "resume();"}
        ],
        "answer": 2,
        "selected": 0
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Question 8: Which cannot directly cause a thread to stop executing?",
        "option": [
          {"optionid": 1, "name": "Calling the SetPriority() method on a Thread object."},
          {"optionid": 2, "name": "Calling the wait() method on an object."},
          {"optionid": 3, "name": "Calling notify() method on an object."},
          {"optionid": 4, "name": "Calling read() method on an InputStream object."}
        ],
        "answer": 3,
        "selected": 0
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Question 9: Which of the following will directly stop the execution of a Thread?",
        "option": [
          {"optionid": 1, "name": "wait()"},
          {"optionid": 2, "name": "notify()"},
          {"optionid": 3, "name": "notifyall()"},
          {"optionid": 4, "name": "exits synchronized code"}
        ],
        "answer": 1,
        "selected": 0
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Question 10: Which method must be defined by a class implementing the java.lang.Runnable interface?",
        "option": [
          {"optionid": 1, "name": "void run()"},
          {"optionid": 2, "name": "public void run()"},
          {"optionid": 3, "name": "public void start()"},
          {"optionid": 4, "name": "void run(int priority)"}
        ],
        "answer": 2,
        "selected": 0
      }
     ]